B. John Hunter

1740 Love Lee Road Morgantown, KY 42261 270-421-7920 | <u>B.JohnHunter71@gmail.com</u> https://venatro71.github.io/Portfolio/ http://twitter.com/@jhunterwebdev www.linkedin.com/in/john-hunter-9b9ob035

PROFILE

Computer technician with 10+ years experience. Energetic problem solver. Effective in a team or independent environment. Highly Organized and detail oriented. Seeking an environment where I can best utilize my skills and develop new ones.

SKILLS

- Solid understanding of Windows 3.11 11, MacOS.
- Advanced troubleshooting skills
- Intermediate networking skills
- Intermediate Linux OS skills

WORK EXPERIENCE

Commonwealth Coders, My Workforce Future. Bowling Green, KY

July 5, 2022 - present

Support Instructor/Grader

- Review all exercises and projects, check code for function and readability.
- Provide feedback to students regarding their exercises and projects
- Assist lead instructor by helping students with questions, coding issues and technical problems.
- Assist with development of course curriculum and assessments.
- Reset, update and distribution of program MacBooks.

Computers Plus, Bowling Green, KY

October 2007 - February 2009

Service Manager/Technician

- Responsible for all repairs, upgrades and service process in service dept.
- Development and implementation of service procedures.
- Training of store personnel in service related issues and process
- Direct customer relations for both sales and service.
- Inventory management

AAA Systems, Bowling Green, KY

June 2001 - September 2003

Service Technician/ Installer

- Installation and service of: residential and commercial security and fire systems, access control systems, CCTV systems.
- Supervised crews and trained new employees.
- Direct customer relations

EDUCATION

ITT Technical College, San Diego, Ca

Sept 1991 – Jun 1993

Electronics Engineering

· Studied electrical circuit design

Commonwealth Coders

Jan 2022 - May 2022

 $Web\ Development$

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React, JavaScript, Python

Hack the Box Academy

Current

Certified Ethical Hacker

Linux OS, BASH scripting, network analysis.